Personal Information

Name/Surname : Nasuh Dinçer Birth Date : 29.03.1999

Nationality : Turkish (with Austria Student Visa)

Address : Vienna, Austria
Phone : +43 6609709300
GitHub : NasuhDincer

E-mail Address : nasuhdinceriletisim@gmail.com

LinkedIn: LinkedIn ProfileWebsite: www.nasuhdincer.com



SUMMARY

Software Engineer with 3 Years of Experience in Software & Web Development, UI Design, and Data Science

SOFTWARE **S**KILLS

Programming Skills

: Java • C/C++ • JavaScript • Python • SQL • HTML • CSS • Assembly • R

Other Skills

: Git • GitHub • GitLab • Linux • UML • Data Structures • Algorithms • Trading • Bioinformatics •

Microsoft Tools

EXPERIENCE

03.2021-11.2023 Software Engineer / Co-Founder Infleap

- Co-founded Infleap, a CPI-based affiliate marketing platform for apps and influencers, with a team
 of four
- Focused on software development, including link generation, deep-links, callback functions, full-stack web development, marketing, and app development
- Successfully created and incorporated four companies and established agreements with over 100 influencers
- Achieved acceptance into Queen's University Innovation Center
- Utilized Technical Skills: JavaScript, React.js, Node.js, PostgreSQL

12.2022-05.2023 Web Developer

FourStep

- Developed fast, real-time websites primarily for media clients in Turkey using Joomla and WordPress
- Collaborated with clients to customize website templates, incorporating HTML, CSS, and JavaScript for bespoke features
- Worked in a team with a Designer and a Senior Engineer
- Notable Project: Leuze Seminar
- **Utilized Technical Skills:** WordPress, Joomla, Hostinger, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Tailwind, Bootstrap

09.2022-12.2022 Software Engineer

YapıKredi Bank

- Continued from internship to remote web development role focusing on stock and foreign exchange screens using Java Spring
- Integrated a widget plugin developed during the internship
- Participated in an Agile team consisting of 14 engineers and 5 business analysts
- **Utilized Technical Skills:** Java Spring, Jira, Microsoft Office Suite

08.2022-09.2022 UI Development Intern

Iotform

- Contributed as a junior UI developer in the revenue team, focusing on CSS, HTML, and JavaScript without libraries.
- Developed both desktop and mobile pages.
- Created a pricing dashboard using React.js with a team of three interns.
- Utilized Technical Skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, Canva, Figma, Jira

05.2022-08.2022 Software Engineering Intern YapıKredi Bank

- Developed real-time market monitoring features using Android Studio and Kotlin
- Designed and implemented a widget for tracking stocks and foreign exchange rates, reaching over 1 million users annually
- Collaborated with 9 engineers from top Turkish universities to complete the project in 1.5 months
- Utilized Technical Skills: Android Studio, Emulators, Kotlin, Java, Firebase

06.2021-08.2021 Software Engineering Intern NTT Data

- Worked with SAP Fiori and SAP ABAP programming languages to provide SAP consultancy solution
- Developed a project for Şişecam, a leading glassware manufacturer, to optimize customer, product, and employee management pages after attending 18 training sessions
- Utilized Technical Skills: SAP ABAP, SAP Fiori

EDUCATION

03.2024-Present Master's Degree in Computer Science Vienna University

09.2017-06.2023 Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science (Full Scholarship with 325th rank among 2.2m students) Bilkent University (240 ECTS, EU Accredited)

- Significant Projects:
 - Recomoda React Native, Node.js, Express.js, Python, MongoDB, Redux (September 2022 May 2023)
 - Online Learning Platform PHP, Python, SOL, HTML, CSS (January 2022 June 2022)
 - Student Club Management System HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Java Spring, PostgreSQL (September 2021 December 2021)
 - Smart Home Systems Android Studio, Java, Firebase, Proteus, Arduino (February 2020 July 2020)

QUALIFICATIONS

STRONG PERSONAL CHARACTERISTICS

Diligent
 Eager-to-learn
 Sociable
 Inquisitive
 Solution-oriented
 Adventurous
 Lively

LANGUAGES

Turkish – Native • **English** – C1

LEISURE ACTIVITIES

- Exploring new places and different cuisines
- Engaging in history and philosophy (reading)
- Orienteering
- Hiking
- Financial markets and trading

VOLUNTARY ACTIVITIES

- Work and Travel, worked 4 months in Stop and Shop Market and Hatchs Package store in Nantucket Island/MA/USA (2023)
- Work and Travel, worked 4 months in Stop and Shop Market and The Beet Restaurant in Nantucket Island/MA/USA (2019)
- Voluntary teacher who taught design, coding, and robotics lessons to primary and secondary school students in the technology laboratories established by the T3 foundation
- Volunteer in TDP, The Sun Rises From The Village, Volunteer Grandchild, Friendship without Barriers
- Co-Founder, Chairman of the Supervisory Board, Bilkent Blockchain Society
- Co-Founder, Chief of Blockchain and Finance, Bilkent SSRS
- Member, IEEE Society, Young Entrepreneurs Society, Social Awareness Projects